{
    "id": "135fc87d0c7543eaa1397f0247fe6e80",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Get your big feet …………………… my flowers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We need three meters ……………………… the windows.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "among",
                "between"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is something …………………. the piano.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "under",
                "underneath",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I had to get up ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at the night",
                "in the night"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I can run 400 meters ………………… about one minute.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am at home ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "every evening",
                "on every evening"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t forget to signal when …………………… . right.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "turning",
                "you are turning",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Life would be more peaceful without ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the phone",
                "phone",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Try ……………….. something.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and speak",
                "to speak",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You have eaten …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all a loaf",
                "a whole loaf",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}